Finding Aid for Athletic Department (University of Michigan) records, 1860-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sports Information Office, 1860-
  - Field Hockey
    - Photos
      - Portraits and Action Photos
        - 2001
          - Wolverine Magazine NCAA Champion cover and article, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
        - 2002
          - Headshots 4/8/2002 (Box 263)
            (14 players and 3 coaches)
          - USA Hockey and Central Michigan 8/23/2002, 9/7/2002 (Box 263)
            (head shots, game action, also includes Men's Ice Hockey coat and tie shots)
          - Ball State 9/8/2002, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Northeastern and Ohio State 9/22/2002, 9/27/2002, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Michigan State 10/4/2002, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
        - 2003
          - North Carolina 8/31/2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Wake Forest 9/1/2003, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - New Hampshire 9/14/2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Maryland 9/20/2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Iowa 10/4/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Penn State 11/3/2003, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - NCAA Semi-Final, Wake Forest 11/21/2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
            (copyright Steve Frischling)
          - NCAA Semi-Final, Wake Forest 11/21/2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
            (copyright Thom Kendall)
        - 2004
          - 2004 Team and headshots, cs only, NIS 15969 (Box 263)
            (headshots May be only incoming freshmen)
          - 2004 Head shots and copies of game action cds, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - CMU 9/17/2004, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Syracuse 9/10/2004, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Old Dominion 9/11/2004, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Harvard 10/3/2004, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Pacific 10/9/2004, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Michigan State 10/16/2004, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Maryland 10/17/2004, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - 5hio State 10/23/2004 (Box 263)
          - 2005 (Box 263)
          - Field Hockey Facilities (field, locker room, lounge) 7/27/2005 (Box 263)
          - Team photos, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Mimi (Ohio) 9/9/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Vermont 9/18/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Indiana 9/30/2005 1 cd (Box 263)
          - Penn State 10/2/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Connecticut 10/9/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Iowa 10/28/2004, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Louisville 10/30/2005, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Iowa 11/4/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Penn State 11/5/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Indiana 11/6/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
        - 2006
          - Team and group photos and headshots 8/23/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Kent State 9/6/2006 (Box 263)
          - Ball State 9/15/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Louisville 9/17/2006, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Michigan State 10/6/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Central Michigan 10/10/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Virginia Commonwealth 10/19/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Ohio State 10/22/2006, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Northwestern, 10/2/9/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Big Ten Banquet 11/2/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Iowa (Big Ten Tournament) 11/3/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Iowa vs Penn State (Big Ten Championship) 11/5/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
        - 2007
          - Team and group photos and headshots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - North Carolina 8/25/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Wake Forest, 8/126/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Temple 8/30/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Old Dominion 9/7/2007, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Connecticut 9/9/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Iowa 9/21/2007, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Penn State 9/23/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - "Texas BBQ", 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Miami (Ohio) 9,30/2007, cs only (Box 263)
          - Indiana 10/12/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Big Ten Tournament, Penn State and Ohio State 11/2/2007-11/4/2007, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
            (copyright Walt Middleton)
          - NCAA First Round, Ohio State 11/10/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
            (copyright Eric Bronson)
          - NCAA Second Round, Wake Forest 11/11/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
        - 2008
          - Team photo and headshots 8/21/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Stanford 9/5/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Maryland,9/7/2008, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - California 9/25/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Northwestern 9/27/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Temple, 10/32008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Ohio State 10/5/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Michigan State 10/17/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Kent State 10/19/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Miami (Ohio), 10,31 2008, 5 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
          - Big Ten Tournament, Ohio State 11/6/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
        - 2000
          - Team photo and headshots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 263)
    - Results
      - 1973-1978 (Box 154)
      - 1978 (Box 154)
      - 1979 (Box 154)
      - 1980 (Box 154)
      - 1982 (Box 154)
      - 1983 (Box 154)
      - 1984 (Box 154)
      - 1985 (Box 154)
      - 1986 (Box 154)
      - 1987 (Box 154)
      - 1988 (Box 154)
      - 1989 (Box 154)
      - 1990, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - 1991 (Box 154)
      - 1992 (Box 154)
      - 1993 (Box 154)
      - 1994 (Box 154)
      - 1994 (Box 154)
      - 1995 (Box 154)
      - 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 154)
      - 2000 (Box 154)
      - 2001 (Box 154)
      - 2002 (Box 154)
      - 2003 (Box 154)
      - 2004 (Box 154)
  - Golf-women
    - Media Guides
      - 1981/82-1982/83, 1985/86-1987/88, 1990/91-1994/95, 1996/97-1998/99 (Box 112)
      - 1999/00-2001/02 (Box 112)
      - 2002/03-2004/05 (Box 112)
      - 2005/06 (Box 112)
    - Photographs
      - Team Photos
        - 1978/7 1979/80-1980/81, 1983/84, 1986/87, 1988/89-1990/91, 1992/93-1997/98 (Box 112)
        - 1998/99- (Box 112)
      - Portraits and action shots Prints
        - Coaches (Box 112)
        - 1977/78 (Box 112)
        - 1981/82 (Box 112)
        - 1982/83 (Box 112)
        - 1983/84 (Box 112)
        - 1985/86 (Box 112)
        - 1986/87 (Box 112)
        - 1988/89 (Box 112)
        - 1989/90 (Box 112)
        - 1990/91 (Box 112)
        - 1992/93 (Box 112)
        - 1993/94 (Box 112)
        - 1994/95 (Box 112)
        - 1995/96 (Box 112)
        - 1996/97 (Box 112)
        - 1997/98 (Box 112)
        - 1998/99 (Box 112)
        - 1999/00 (Box 112)
        - 2000/01 (Box 112)
        - 2000/01 (headshots, negs) (Box 112)
        - 2001/02 (Box 112)
        - 20002 NCAA Tournament (Box 112)
        - 2002/03 (headshot contact sheets) (Box 112)
      - Portraits and action shots-Digital
        - 2002/03 (Box 223)
        - 2004/05
          - CD #1, Fall 2004 (Box 223)
            (includes: Lady Northern Marry Fossum Invit., Lansing; Lady Razorback Inv.; Legends, Indiana; Edwin Watts, .S.C.)
          - CD #2 Fall and Spring 2004 (include same as CD#1 plus Central District Classic, FL; Baylor Tapatio Springs Shootout (Box 223)
          - CD #3, Big Ten Tournament Banquet (Box 223)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 223)
    - Video/DVD
      - 2004/05
        - Season Video (Michigan Sports Television) (Box 160)
        - Big Ten Tournament (Box 160)
          (still photos with musical tack)
    - Press Releases & Clippings
      - 1995/96 (Box 112)
      - 1996/97 (Box 112)
      - 2001/02 (Box 112)
    - Meet results
      - 1977/78 (Box 148)
      - 1978/79 (Box 148)
      - 1979/80 (Box 148)
      - 1980/81 (Box 148)
      - 1981/82 (Box 148)
      - 1982/83 (Box 148)
      - 1983/84 (Box 148)
      - 1984/85 (Box 148)
      - 1985/86 (Box 148)
      - 1986/87 (Box 148)
      - 1987/88 (Box 148)
      - 1988/89 (Box 148)
      - 1989/90 (Box 148)
      - 1990/91 (Box 148)
      - 1991/92 (Box 148)
      - 1992/93 (Box 148)
      - 1993/94 (Box 148)
      - 1994/95 (Box 148)
      - 1995/96 (Box 148)
      - 1996/97 (Box 148)
      - 1997/98 (Box 148)
      - 1998/99 (Box 148)
      - 1999/00 (Box 148)
      - 2000/01 (Box 149)
      - 2001/02 (includes NCAA tournament) (Box 149)
      - 2002/03 (Box 149)
      - 2003/04, 2 folders (Box 149)
      - 2003/04, 2 folders (Box 149)
      - 2004/05
        - Meet Results (Box 149)
        - Meet information (Box 149)
        - Compiled Tournament Results (Box 149)
        - Season in Review (Box 149)
          (clippings, player bios, press releases)
      - 2005/06
        - Meet results (Box 218)
        - Compiled Tournament Results (Box 218)
        - Season in Review (Box 218)
      - 2006/07
        - Meet Results, 2 folders (Box 218)
  - Gymnastics-women
    - Media Guides
      - 1981-1991 (Box 64-B)
      - 1992-1994 (Box 64-B)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 64-B)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 64-B)
      - 1999 (Box 64-B)
      - 2000 (Box 64-B)
      - 2001 (Box 64-B)
      - 2002 (Box 64-B)
      - 2003 (Box 64-B)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 64-B)
      - 2006 (Box 64-B)
    - Meet Results
      - 1974/75 (Box 65)
      - 1976/77 (Box 65)
      - 1978/79 (Box 65)
      - 1979/80 (Box 65)
      - 1980/81 (Box 65)
      - 1981/82 (Box 65)
      - 1982/83 (Box 65)
      - 1983/84 (Box 65)
      - 1984/85 (Box 65)
      - 1985/86 (Box 65)
      - 1986/87 (Box 65)
      - 1987/88 (Box 65)
      - 1988/89 (Box 65)
      - 1990 (Box 65)
      - 1991
        - 1991 Regular Season Results (Box 65)
        - 1991 Big Ten and NCAA Championship Results (Box 65)
      - 1992
        - 1992 Regular Season Results (Box 65)
        - 1992 Big Ten and NCAA Championship Results (Box 65)
        - 1992 Individual Stats and Rankings (Box 65)
      - 1993
        - 1993 (Box 65)
        - 1993 NCAA Championship Results (Box 65)
        - 1993 Individual Stats (Box 65)
      - 1994
        - 1994 Regular Season Results (Box 65)
        - 1994 Big Ten and NCAA Championship Results (Box 65)
        - 1994 Individual Stats and Rankings (Box 65)
      - 1995
        - 1995 Regular Season Results (Box 65)
        - 1995 Big Ten and NCAA Results (Box 65)
        - 1995 Individual Stats (Box 65)
      - 1996
        - Regular Season, 2 folders (Box 180)
        - Postseason Results (Box 180)
        - Individual Stats (Box 180)
      - 1997
        - 1997, 2 folders (Box 180)
        - 1997 NCAA Championship, Central Region Results (Box 180)
      - 1998
        - 1998 Regular Season Results, 2 folders (Box 180)
        - 1998 NCAA Championship Results (Box 180)
        - 1998 Individual Stats (Box 180)
      - 1999
        - 1999 Regular Season Results, 2 folders (Box 180)
        - 1999 Postseason Results (Box 180)
        - 1999 Final Season Stats Package (Box 180)
      - 2000
        - 2000 Final Season Results (Box 180)
        - 2002 Regular Season Results (Box 180)
        - 2002 Postseason Results (Box 180)
      - 2001
        - 2001 Regular Season Results (Box 180)
        - 2001 Post-Season Results (Box 180)
      - 2002
        - 2002 Regular Season Results (Box 180)
        - 2002 Post-Season Results (Box 180)
      - 2003
        - 2003 Regular Season Results (Box 180)
        - 2003 Postseason Results (Box 180)
      - UM Gymnastics Postseason History 1982-1998 (Box 180)
    - Programs and Post-Season Media Guides
      - 1985-1992 (Box 181)
      - 1993 NCAA Championship Program (Box 181)
      - 1994, 2 folders (Box 181)
      - 1995 (Box 181)
      - 1996 (Box 181)
      - 1997, 2 folders (Box 181)
      - 1998 (Box 181)
      - 1999, 2 folders (Box 181)
      - 2000, 2 folders (Box 181)
      - 2001 (Box 181)
      - 2002 (Box 181)
      - 2003, 2 folders (Box 181)
      - 2008 (Box 13)
    - Photographs
      - Team Photos
        - 1977-1978, 1982 (Box 182)
        - 1992-2004 (Box 182)
      - Portraits and Action Shots
        (contact sheets of "picture day" photos and some prints)
        - Coaches (Box 182)
        - Unidentified (Box 182)
        - 1977/78 (Box 182)
        - 1978/79 (Box 182)
        - 1979/80 (Box 182)
        - 1980/81 (Box 182)
        - 1981/82 (Box 182)
        - 1982/83 (Box 182)
        - 1983/84 (Box 182)
        - 1984/85 (Box 182)
        - 1985/86 (Box 182)
        - 1986/87 (Box 182)
        - 1987/88 (Box 182)
        - 1988/89 (Box 182)
        - 1989/90 (Box 182)
        - 1990/91 (Box 182)
        - 1992 (Box 182)
          (cs, prints, negatives, head shots, meet action)
        - 1993 (Box 182)
          (cs, prints, meet action, posed)
        - 1993 (Box 182)
        - 1993/94 (Box 182)
          (cs, prints, meet action)
        - 1994/95 (Box 182)
        - 1994/95 (Box 182)
        - 1994/95 (Box 182)
          (slides, meet action)
        - 1994/95 NCAA Championship (Box 182)
        - 1996
          - 1996 (Box 182)
            (cs, negatives, meet action)
          - 1996 (Box 182)
            (cs, prints, head shots, meet action)
        - 1997
          - 1997 (Box 182)
          - 1997 (Box 182)
            (prints, head shots, meet action, posed)
        - 1998 (Box 182)
          (prints, head shots, meet action, posed and contact sheets)
        - 1999 (Box 183)
          - 1999 (Box 183)
          - 1999 (Box 183)
        - 2000 (Box 183)
          (prints, meet action)
        - 2001
          - 2001 (Box 183)
            (prints, head shots, pose action)
          - 2001 meet action, miscellaneous, prints and contact sheets (Box 183)
          - 2001 Big Ten Championship, prints (Box 183)
          - 2001 NCAA Championships, prints (Box 183)
        - 2002
          - 2002 meet action (Box 183)
            (cs, digital cs)
            (see box 223 for digital material)
          - 2002 (headshots, posed, groups and miscellaneous) (Box 183)
        - 2003
          - Meet action by photos Kurt Avenda UCLA, Minnesota, N. Illinois, Ohio State, Kent St/W. Virginia, cs and negs (Box 183)
          - Meet action photos by U-M Photo Services (Box 183)
            (cs, negatives prints, meet action)
        - 2002/03-2003/04, 1 volumes (Box 256)
          (contact prints and cds, team ad player photos and game action. also includes media guide files, some files for 2000 and 2001)
        - 2004/05, 1 volumes (Box 256)
          (contact prints and cds, team and player photos and game action. also includes media guide files)
        - 2005/06, 1 volumes (Box 256)
        - 2006/07, 1 volumes (Box 256)
        - 2007/08, 1 volumes (Box 257)
        - 2008/09, 1 volumes (Box 257)
      - Photo Books "Gymnastics Memories"
        - 2009 "Michigan Gymnastics Memories" (Box 257)
        - 2010 "Let's Go Blue: 2010 Michigan Gymnastics" (Box 257)
    - Articles and Releases
      - 1982 Clippings (Box 184)
      - 1991 Releases (Box 184)
      - 1992 Articles (Box 184)
      - 1992 Releases (Box 184)
      - 1993 NCAA Championship Press Clippings, 2 folders (Box 184)
      - 1993 Releases (Box 184)
      - 1994 Releases (Box 184)
      - 1994/95 News Releases (Box 184)
      - 1995 Articles (Box 184)
      - 1996 Articles (Box 184)
      - 1996 News Releases/Info (Box 184)
      - 1997 Articles (Box 184)
      - 1997 Press Releases (Box 184)
      - 1997 Releases, 2 folders (Box 184)
      - 1997 Weekly Releases (Box 184)
      - 1997 NCAA Championship Media Clip Packet (Box 184)
      - 1997 NCAA Championship Media Clip Packet, Central Region (Box 184)
      - 1997 NCAA Championship Releases, Central Region (Box 184)
      - 1998 Media Clips and Articles (Box 184)
      - 1998 News Releases (Box 184)
      - 1998 Weekly Releases, 2 folders (Box 184)
      - 1999 Big Ten Releases (Box 184)
      - 1999 Post-Event Releases (Box 184)
      - 1999 Press Clips (Box 184)
      - 1999 Releases, 2 folders (Box 184)
      - 1999 Weekly Releases (Box 184)
      - 2000, 4 folders (Box 184)
      - 2001, 3 folders (Box 185)
      - 2002, 3 folders (Box 185)
      - 2002 Releases, 2 folders (Box 185)
      - 2003 Releases, 2 folders (Box 185)
    - GymInfo Reports
      - 1997, 3 folders (Box 185)
      - 1998, 1 folders (Box 185)
      - 1999 National Rankings, 2 folders (Box 185)
      - 1999 Regional Rankings (Box 185)
      - 2000 Conference Rankings (Box 185)
      - 2000 National Rankings (Box 185)
      - 2000 Regional Rankings (Box 185)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Calendars 2002, 2004, 2006 (Box 185)
      - NCAA Championship, Central Region, Planning and Promotional Material 1995, 1997 (Box 185)
      - Newsletter 1989-1998 (Box 185)
      - Trading Cards 1998-1999, 2001, 2003-2006 (Box 185)
    - Digital Media
      - Photos and Files
        - 1997 Gymnastic Programs (Box 223)
          (3.5" floppy disk)
        - 2002 Covers (Box 223)
          (CD)
          (posed photographs and IFC facility files)
        - 2003 Media Guide and Covers (Box 223)
          (head shot, meet action, and posed photographs; font documents)
  - Rowing -- women
    - Media Guides
      - 1997-2000 (Box 198)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 198)
      - 2003-2004 (Box 198)
      - 2005 (Box 198)
    - Results
      - 1996/97 (Box 198)
      - 1997/98 (Box 198)
      - 1998/99 (Box 198)
      - 1999/2000 (Box 198)
      - 2000/01 (Box 198)
    - Programs
      - 1998 NCAA Championship Program (Box 198)
      - 1999 NCAA Championship Program (Box 198)
      - 2000 Big Ten and NCAA Championship Programs (Box 198)
      - 2001 Big Ten and NCAA Championship Programs (Box 198)
    - Photographs
      - Team Photographs
        - 1996-2001 (Box 199)
      - Portraits and Action Photos
        - 1996/97, cs, prints, head shots, meet action (Box 199)
        - 1997/98, cs, negatives, prints, head shots, meet action (Box 199)
        - 1998/99, cs, prints, head shots, meet action (Box 199)
        - 1999 NCAA, negatives, prints, slides, meet action (Box 199)
        - 1999/2000, cs, prints, head shots, meet action, posed (Box 199)
        - 1999/2000, negatives, prints, meet action, posed (Box 199)
        - 2000 Big Ten Rowing, prints, meet action (Box 199)
        - 2000 Big Ten Championship, 2 folders negatives, meet action (Box 199)
        - 2000/01, cs, prints, head shots, meet action (Box 199)
    - Articles and Releases
      - 1996/97 Clippings and Releases (Box 199)
      - 1997/98 Clippings and Releases (Box 199)
      - 1998/99 Clippings and Releases (Box 199)
      - 1999/2000 Clippings and Releases (Box 199)
      - 2000/01 Clippings (Box 199)
      - 2000/01 Releases and Big Ten Releases (Box 199)
  - Soccer -- women
    - Media Guides
      - 1994 (Box 150)
        (includes 1989 club sport roster)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 150)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 150)
      - 2003-2004 (Box 150)
      - 2005 (Box 150)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 150)
      (includes blank statistics forms)
    - Programs and Post Season guides
      - 1994-1998 (Box 150)
      - 1999-2001 (Box 150)
      - 2002 (Box 150)
      - 2003 (Box 150)
        (includes Big Ten and NCAA Tournaments)
      - 2004 (Box 150)
    - Photographs
      - Team Photos
        - 1994-2003, 2006 (Box 150)
      - Coaches (Box 150)
      - Portraits and action shots
        - 1994 (Box 150)
        - 1995 (Box 150)
        - 1996 (Box 150)
        - 1997 (Box 150)
        - 1998 (Box 150)
        - 1999 (Box 150)
        - 2000 (Box 150)
        - 2001 (Box 150)
        - 2002 (Box 150)
          (contact sheet and digital files on CD, team, headshots and game action, photos by Martin Vloet and Amir Gamzu)
    - Digital Media
      - Portraits and action shots
        - 2002, 12 optical disks CD-Rs (Box 150)
          (headshots and game action, photos by Martin Vloet and Amir Gamzu)
        - 2003, 4 optical disks CD-Rs (Box 150)
          (includes media, guide files, releases)
        - 2004, 2 optical disks CD-Rs (Box 150)
          (includes media guide files, season summaries etc)
        - 2005, 1 optical disks CD-Rs (Box 150)
          (2005 media guide files)
        - 2003/04 Photo Book, contact sheets & digital files (CDs (Box 229)
          (team photos, headshots, game action)
        - 2005/06 Photo Book, contact sheets & digital files (CDs (Box 229)
          (team photo, headshots, game action, Big Ten Tournament)
        - 2007 Photo Book, contact sheets & digital files (CDs (Box 229)
        - 2008 Photo Book, contact sheets & digital files (CDs (Box 229)
          (team photos, headshots, game action, coach photos (Greg Ryan)
        - 2009 Photo Book, contact sheets & digital files (Box 229)
          (game action, Arkansas game only)
    - Press Releases and Clippings
      - 1994 (Box 151)
      - 1995 (Box 151)
      - 1996 (Box 151)
      - 1997, 2 folders (Box 151)
      - 1998 (Box 151)
      - 1999, 2 folders (Box 151)
      - 2000 (Box 151)
      - 2001, 2 folders (Box 151)
      - 2003 (Box 151)
        (as pdf file in box 223)
    - Results
      - 1994-2002 Summary team and Individual Statistics (Box 152)
      - 1994 (Box 152)
      - 1995 (Box 152)
      - 1996 (Box 152)
      - 1997 (Box 152)
      - 1999 (Box 152)
      - 2000 (Box 152)
      - 2001 (Box 152)
      - 2002 (Box 152)
        (Post-Season Media Guide)
      - 2003 (Box 152)
        (Season recap)
      - 2004 (Box 152)
      - 2005 (Box 152)
      - 2008 (Box 152)
      - 2009 (Box 152)
  - Softball
    - Media Guides
      - 1979, 1981-1988 (Box 141)
        (some photocopies)
      - 1989-1992 (Box 141)
      - 1993-1996 (Box 141)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 141)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 141)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 141)
      - 2003-2004 (Box 141)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 141)
    - Tournament Media Guides
      - 1991/1992 (Box 141)
      - 1992/1993 (Box 141)
      - 1994/1995 (Box 141)
      - 1995/1996 (Box 141)
      - 1996/1997 (Box 141)
      - 1997/1998 (Box 141)
      - 1999/2000 (Box 141)
      - 2001/2002 (Box 141)
    - Programs
      (includes College World Series Regionals)
      - 1982-1984 (Box 142)
      - 1988-1991 (Box 142)
      - 1992-1994 (Box 142)
      - 1994/1995 (Box 142)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 142)
      - 1997/1998 (Box 142)
      - 1998/1999 (Box 142)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 142)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 142)
      - 2003-2006 (Box 142)
    - Miscellaneous
      - History (Box 142)
        (includes stats over time and information on alums)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 142)
        (includes blank score cards, recruit signee forms, Certificate of Tribute from the state of Michigan and a congratulatory statement from Representative Dingell on winning the 2005 World Series)
      - Posters /Schedules
        - 1983-1984, 1995, 1997-1998, 2000 (Folder 8)
    - Photographs
      - Team photos
        - 1978-1979, 1980-1982 1983/1984 1987-1990, 1992-2002 (Box 143)
      - Champion teams
        - 1978-1999 (Box 143)
      - Coaches (Box 143)
      - Portraits and Action shots
        - 1978-1981 (Box 143)
        - 1981/1982 (Box 143)
        - 1982/1983 (Box 143)
        - 1983/1984 (Box 143)
        - 1984/1985 (Box 143)
        - 1985/1986 (Box 143)
        - 1986/1987 (Box 143)
        - 1987/1988 (Box 143)
        - 1988/1989 (Box 143)
        - 1989/1990 (Box 143)
        - 1990/1991 (Box 143)
        - 1991/1992 (Box 143)